<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="app_name">Rom Search Plus</string>
<string name="email">Email:</string>
<string name="password">Password:</string>
<string name="login">Login</string>
<string name="loginMessage">Logging in...</string>
<string name="savePasswordCheck">Save Password</string>
<string name="pleaseLogin">Please login:</string>
<string name="register">Register...</string>
<string name="help1">I have selected different ROM categories for each ROM website. If the background of a website is red, then it is currently down. You can see which consoles each website supports by the console icons underneath each website. Whether or not you can use the search functions on a website is indicated by the word \&quot;Search\&quot; above a ROM provider.\n\nCertain ROMs can be downloaded/extracted directly into the specified ROMs folder, whereas some websites require you to download the files via their website. In order to do this you must:\n\n* Locate the link on the webpage\n* Click and hold until the context menu appears\n* Select \&quot;Save Link\&quot;\n* Retrieve your file using an unzip app (e.g. AndroZip) from the /downloads/ folder\n\nI have provided direct links to these programs on the Android Market in the Preferences.</string>
<string name="help2"></string>
<string name="eula_rombay">Terms Of Use\n\nAcceptance of Terms\nAccess to and use of this Website (the \"Site\") is subject to the following terms and conditions, which you are deemed to have accepted in full by accessing the Site. If you do not wish to accept these terms and conditions you should leave the Site immediately. \n\nAvailability\nromBay.com will endeavour to ensure that the Site is accessible for 24 hours a day. However, romBay.com will not be liable if, for any reason, the Site is unavailable at any time or for any period. This includes server upgrades and other such essential maintenance. romBay.com will have the right to suspend access to the Site temporarily or permanently and without notice. romBay.com will not be liable for loss or damages arising in contract, tort or otherwise if the Site becomes unavailable or is suspended for any reason. This includes complete exclusion of liability if you have purchased an upgraded account and are unable to access the site.\n\n Liability\nromBay.com accepts no responsibility for tontent of any other site to which a hypertext link to or from the Site exits. romBay.com cannot warrant that the Site is free of technical defects of any description and will not be responsible for any technical problems arising from the use of the Site. \n\nAcceptable Use\nAny user who\'s levels of use of the system is so high that it adversely affect other users will be liable to have their account terminated. This includes, but is not limited to, free account users with unusually high levels of traffic. Any user who causes disruption for other users, violates the privacy of any user or corrupts data of other users either directly or indirectly (such as by introducing a virus via our system) will be subject to legal action and of course will have their account terminated and IP forwarded to the relevant authorities. romBay.com reserves the right to terminate any free account at any time. We will always endeavour to provide a reason for any account terminations, but we make no guarantees that this will always be possible. All users agree only to download files for which they own a licence. In addition, all users agree not to distribute their account log in details. Furthermore, all users agree by signing up that they may receive occasional mailings direct from romBay.com regarding site updates and status. Inline with our privacy policy, your email address is not distributed to any third parties. Violation of our AUP will result in instant account termination. Please refer to the relevant pages once you have logged in to your free account for details of our payment refund policy for upgraded accounts.</string>
</resources>
